<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hot Spot</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="Taroko">When Taroko National Park was established on November 28, l986, it was of special significance for the environmental protection movement in Taiwan: it showed that both the public and the government agencies had realized that against the background of the nation\'s four decades of extraordinary economic success, serious damage was being done to its natural resources.\n According to the National Park Act of the Republic of China (passed in l972), parks are established to protect the natural scenery, historic relics and wildlife; to conserve natural resources; and to facilitate scientific research and promote environmental education.</string>
    <string name="Shei_Pa">When we are trying to gain some understanding of any national park, it is useful to consider in what country and what area the park lies. Shei-Pa National Park is in Taiwan, so a quick review of Taiwan may be helpful here. \nTaiwan, or Formosa as it used to be called, is an island about 160 kilometers off the southeast coast of Mainland China, between Japan and Philippines on a line running north-southwest. It is approximately 36,000 square kilometers in size, about the same size as Holland, and a little larger than Massachusetts and Connecticut States combined. Three quarters of the land area is mountainous, much of it too steep to be cultivated easily. There are more than 200 peaks over 3,000 meters in altitude. The highest of them, Jade Mountain reaches 3,952 meters.</string>
    <string name="Yushan">872 haben die Vereinigten Staaten von Amerika den ersten Nationalpark der Welt, den Yellow Stone National Park, gegründet. Im darauffolgenden Jahrhundert wurden überall auf der Welt Tausende Nationalparks eröffnet.Diese Parks verteilen sich auf mehrere hundert Länder, die subpolare, gemäßigte und tropische Klimazonen abdecken. Sie beinhalten eine große Vielfalt an ökologischen und geographischen Landschaften, zu denen Berge, Seen, Gletscher, Vulkane, Wälder, Sümpfe, Graslandschaften und Schluchten zählen.</string>
    <string name="Kenting">The park covers about 181 square kilometres (70 sq mi) of land, 152 square kilometres (59 sq mi) of sea, weighing in at 333 square kilometres (129 sq mi) combined. Nan Wan and Banana Bay is surrounded by the Pacific Ocean, the Taiwan Strait, and the Luzon Strait. The park is 90 kilometres (56 mi) away from Kaohsiung, 140 kilometres (87 mi) away from Tainan.\n The landscape boasted by Kenting National Park is divided into two parts by the long and narrow Hengchun Longitudinal Valley Plain that extends from north to south. With coral sea cliffs teemed with fringing reefs along the west coast, the park features a large number of mountains in the north, and coral tablelands and foothills in the south. The plain, which is formed by fault valleys, has a vast lake called Longlyuantan, together with rising coral tablelands and limestone caves to the east. The east side of the coral tablelands features unique sand rivers and sand waterfalls formed by the combined effects of winds and rivers, as well as coral cliffs, sunken caves and stalactites.</string>
</resources>
